<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Notes of Camus: A critical examination.</title>
    <link href="/Notes-Camus_a_critical_examination/"/>
    <url>/Notes-Camus_a_critical_examination/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Chapter-1-experimental-sources"><a href="#Chapter-1-experimental-sources" class="headerlink" title="Chapter 1 experimental sources"></a>Chapter 1 experimental sources</h2><blockquote><p>Like Dewey, for example, Camus treats theories as hypotheses and treats goals as guidance to action, while requiring that values be grounded in and tested by experience.</p></blockquote><h2 id="Chapter-2-the-death-of-god"><a href="#Chapter-2-the-death-of-god" class="headerlink" title="Chapter 2 the death of god"></a>Chapter 2 the death of god</h2><blockquote><p>We are adrift in a Newtonian world of matter in motion following purposeless natural laws, which during the course of Darwinian evolution has given birth to sensitive and reflective animals who differ from the rest of creation solely in the knowledge of their impending death. It’s only the matter of time. </p></blockquote><blockquote><p>To encounter absurdity is only the begining. The begining of awareness; the begining of refelction of the long and arduous effort to find our way out of the dead end which is the nihilistic conclusion to the death of transcendent values.</p></blockquote><p>Why talking about suicide, because it “involves an abdication of the struggle to give meaning to our life on its own terms”. </p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Too Far Gone</title>
    <link href="/TooFarGone/"/>
    <url>/TooFarGone/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>“Men should be men”. But “Men are not allowed to show their weakness”   </p><p>So I let my weakness grow too much so that it has impeded my should-have masculinity.</p><p>“The unexamined life is not worth living”. But too much examination can be harmful(思而不学则殆).</p><p>So I forgot the habit of self-reflction and let myself gone too far.</p><p>Probably I should learn more about Hegel’s dialectics to balance my stance.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Nostalgia of The Rebel</title>
    <link href="/The-Nostalgia-of-The-Rebel/"/>
    <url>/The-Nostalgia-of-The-Rebel/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>People talk about Camus when it comes to a serious post-modernism situation. They parade the independence of their minds as if that is something valuable. Oh, but my friend, you are just another drunken guy just you get drunk with Nietzsche and Camus.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
